Friends, today we are going to talk about this stock market paradise.
If you look at it,
you will see a lot of IPOs in the market
and you are going to
see many more in the coming days.
We are going to discuss all of them later in the video.
But whatever ID you will
see, if you
look at it currently, we are applying for a GMP here.
Whatever you see,
you should apply for GMP in almost all the IPOs
right now
because you will see many companies here which are
loss-making companies. Even then,
you will see their GMP which is very good.
If we do not have the quarterly results of the company, then
we cannot stay in it long-term.
So we are going to talk about all the IPOs
and today you got to see the
profession of you go fashion here
because it was seen in the listing here
and you completed the listing and work here. It is a
very good thing. Congratulations to you from my side
because you
booked a profit here and in 10 days you
Quite, I have got it, what you will get
to see in one year, two years, 15 years, you will get to
see it in just 10 days and
booking listing gains is never a bad thing
in any IPO because
see, according to GMP, if we are
applying for an IPO here, then
it is a very good thing that we get out after listing and
work because then you will
not be too stressed about
how your company is going to form, so it is
good if you have done half the booking,
but if you did it and did not do it, then
you can do it in the future also, there is no
problem, if you
want to stay long term, then for that we will have to
check the fundamentals
of the company properly, if we talk about show it, you are
seeing it in the market, one if
you see Anand Rathi, if you or you will get to
see it from 2nd December to 4th December,
you can apply for it here, you
can apply till the next time,
why see the price band, Rs.530
minimum and the national Rs.550 high
band  You can do this here, I will
not see you, for a total you get
to see an offer for sale and I will
make a video about this in full detail about Anand Rathi IPO so that
you do not face any problem,
if you look at the face value, very rarely you get to see
that the face value of one share is
₹5, mostly you
get to see a face value of ₹10 for one share, which
is very good in retail allocations, 35 per
cent, that is, your chances of getting
65 percent from housing development or motors will be
seen as allotment here and
you will get an allotment from the exact 5 percent for you, it is to be held
on both NSE and BSE, if we talk about the
IPO of Anand Math, if you
see it today, 30th November, Dhaniya,
you will see it running on seats today
and it started from today, so now whatever
updates you get from MP, I will tell you about
Rs.80 close to you  It is seen that
currently the next company is going to have its IPO
or you will see that it opens here tomorrow, you will get to
see a
very wonderful IPO of Teja Industries,
you can subscribe to it from tomorrow and
its last date is till Thursday, September 3, this is the third, at this time
you are getting to see the closing date, if you see the
price, if you see it, it is 443, then on foot and price and
453, there is no disturbance in the share price of fresh juice here,
you will get to see the total offer for sale and here if you
see the agreement of hello, here it is 35 per cent
of yourself, you will see that the total IPO
decision is of 619 crores, it is very big,
if you get to see it and it will also
come on both NSE and BSE and if you
see the face value of one share, then friends,
you will get to see that if we
see here how you get to see the GMP
of Dega Industries, then you will
see that today remember that on 30th November,
it was trading at ₹300  It is being said that the price is increasing which is constant
from last day so it is good that you will see the jam also
increasing it will not decrease here
because industries will give a lot, this thing here
is the fundamental of stock company,
however I am going to make a video about your industries
so that you will
not have any confusion about industries, so currently
you will see or Jio 4G MP
is running setting stop on 30th November,
if we talk about the next IPO then you
get to see Star Health, it has already
opened for you, if you have applied then
I made a video for that, you should have
seen it first, if
you have applied then fine now
you are gone but according to me
you should just stay away from
this IPO, if you see
that you can subscribe, then you can do it till today i.e. 30th
November 2nd December, you
apply for Raju and its 870 aspect and 9
pm prizes fresh in it is of two thousand crores
and if you see it then it is of 5249 crores,
whenever if you get to see
Again, it should always be higher and
its officer is higher, so
here we
see a lot of negative things.
If you ask for my opinion in IPO, I would say that
you should not apply for Star Health. It is
possible that you will get this -
see how much has gone on the table.
Now we are going to see about Star Health. The
promoter of this company is Rakesh Jhunjhunwala ji
and when do you have your life behind this name,
look at the symptoms. I am not against him or anything else,
I am just saying that you should
not always look at the promoter. It is a
good thing in the company that the promoter of the company is the one who is the promoter,
but we
cannot invest in a company only because of them. It is possible that
you get this motivation here
that if Bindu Bala ji has
invested here then we will also do so, so that is
not a good thing. Here you should
not apply by looking at any promoter.
Everyone backs some company or the other,
but it becomes very important to understand the performance of all the companies.
If you can do it properly, then you can
add the company properly.  After all, you will become the next
Rakesh Jhunjhunwala, it is possible that
you may leave him behind and you may become even bigger, so for this
you will have to do your own special work
and my opinion is that the
fundamentals of Star Health that I have seen, you should
not apply them here,
if you see the election from my side, you will see 10%, the
face value of one share is ₹10,
you will see the
size of Thank you, what is 7250 crores and it will be
listed on both NSE and BSE,
if we talk about Gym Star, it is its
jam, if you see this then you will
see above 20 here, which is the
stand that you have seen today, on 30th
November, you will see it for the first time, which
you were seeing for the continuation of November,
so it is running at Rs.20, all that
in the coming time you may see zero,
it may
even go up, but from my side, it will be that
you should be a little cautious of Star Hash
and this is my personal opinion, I am
not saying that you should not  If you wish,
you can apply for a
day. If I mention today
's subscription, here you will see if you
see the subscription, from the
sowing side, it is zero percent here
and from the applying side,
see point zero percent. Still, we
always go ahead with weight loss because it happens
very quickly. We have to apply for any IPO, Maya
Height. So, do this, look at
this company thoroughly,
understand it fundamentally, check it. I
made a video, but very few people have
seen the video here, and then the same people will say
that when we get trapped, we suffer a loss, what should we do? Did
you understand the company first? You should
first understand how the company is
strong. So, this point
4% is seen here, points 60 are
seen here, the
employees have subscribed point zero three times here.
Now see, the employees have
reduced here and you retailers have gone out of business, so
this is causing problems here.
This thing can create total, if you see the
point way here the time is subscribed, that is,
if you see this subscription, then
you do not get to see it well, people are
staying away from this IPO, if we talk about the next IPO, then
you will get to see it,
Adani Wilmar's IQ, its official date has
not been released as to when you
can see it, although
its off serial date will be released soon,
but if you look at today on 30th November, then
its G ampere has again increased by ₹10 in an
increment of ₹10, it has become ₹100,
today which is the last one, if you see, it was
110th, so you have
seen an increment in it now, although Adani
Group's IPO is about to come, so you are going to
see good
news about it, and
if you watch it currently, it will be very
active,
all these decimal times that you get to see will be cut by one,
for that what you have to do is subscribe to the channel
So that
whatever videos I upload,
you keep getting updates of them so that you do
not have any problem,
in understanding any company, it is fundamentally important to check the lines that they do, that
we get to see the company in this way, so you can watch
all these videos about it and if
you have not created a demat account yet, then
I have given the length in the description box, you
can create your demat account in half the stock, it is
very good, you
get to see a brokerage house, it is very easy here you
can start types of investments and
so go and create your demat account
and do investment distance